<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-05-12T22:21:56+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">harrypujols</title><subtitle>The personal Web site of Harry Pujols, a tech developer and artist.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Everything sucks. My retreat from social media</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/everything-sucks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Everything sucks. My retreat from social media" /><published>2024-05-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/everything-sucks</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/everything-sucks.html">&lt;p&gt;Is it me, or every tech company we used to like has turned into shit the last couple of years?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social media is no longer about being social, it’s about influencers, content creators and the shitshow in the comments. Even so, the user experience is far superior from just browsing the Web. Web sites are unusable, looking like Christmas trees, infested with popups and ads, sometimes auto playing videos with full audio. You no longer own anything, the music you hear, the movies you watch, the applications in your laptop, and even the games you play for some, are all under a subscription plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;youtube&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the platform for viral videos, it has been rendered unwatchable, with a flood of commercial interruptions every 10 seconds, to goad you to subscribe to YouTube Premium.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;twitter&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I followed David Bowie, Alejandro Jodorowsky, Trent Reznor, David Lynch and his on-brand daily weather updates. Sports scores, live commentary on the new episode of Breaking Bad. Now, as Xitter, it’s the front of a cyberwarfare war the far Right has declared on the world, with the assitance of the Russian military and hedonistic ultra-rich misantropes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apple&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company that invented the mind-control devices we now call phones, is the master of planned obsolence. There’s the technology to store your entire record collection and photos in a small device, but why do it if you can pay a few dollars a month for cloud storage? Why have a headphone jack when you can sell proprietary, overpriced wireless headphones? Their only new products in a decade are an ugly rectangular watch and a comically expensive VR set.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="posts" /><summary type="html">Is it me, or every tech company we used to like has turned into shit the last couple of years?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/posts/everything-sucks.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/posts/everything-sucks.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Harry Pujols has entered the group.</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Harry Pujols has entered the group." /><published>2024-05-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/hello-world.html"></content><author><name></name></author><category term="posts" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/posts/interested-girl.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/posts/interested-girl.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>